<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>
    <category>
        <pattern>HELLO</pattern>
        <template>Hi there! I’m Healthy FitAI! How can I assist you on your fitness journey today?</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT IS YOUR NAME</pattern>
        <template>I am Healthy FitAI, your virtual fitness and health assistant!</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>HOW ARE YOU</pattern>
        <template>I’m doing great, thanks for asking! Ready to help you with your health goals!</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>HOW ARE YOU DOING</pattern>
        <template>I’m doing great, thanks for asking! Ready to help you with your health goals!</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>BYE</pattern>
        <template>Goodbye! Stay healthy and fit!</template>
    </category>
       <category>
       <pattern>Hi</pattern>
       <template>Hi there! I’m Healthy FitAI! How can I assist you on your fitness journey today?</template>
   </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU DO</pattern>
        <template>I can provide workout tips, healthy recipes, and answer your fitness questions!</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>GIVE ME A WORKOUT PLAN</pattern>
        <template>Sure! What are your fitness goals? (e.g., weight loss, muscle gain, endurance)</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT SHOULD I EAT FOR BREAKFAST</pattern>
        <template>A healthy breakfast could include oatmeal with fruits, Greek yogurt, or a smoothie packed with greens!</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>GIVE ME A HEALTHY RECIPE</pattern>
        <template>How about a quinoa salad? Mix quinoa with veggies like cucumbers, tomatoes, and a squeeze of lemon!</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>HOW DO I LOSE WEIGHT</pattern>
        <template>To lose weight, focus on a balanced diet, regular exercise, and staying hydrated. It’s important to create a calorie deficit!</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>HOW DO I BUILD MUSCLE</pattern>
        <template>Building muscle requires strength training, adequate protein intake, and sufficient rest. Are you following a specific routine?</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT IS A GOOD EXERCISE FOR STRESS RELIEF</pattern>
        <template>Yoga and deep breathing exercises are great for relieving stress. A brisk walk in nature can also help!</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>TELL ME ABOUT NUTRITION</pattern>
        <template>Nutrition is key to a healthy lifestyle. Focus on whole foods, plenty of fruits and vegetables, lean proteins, and healthy fats!</template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>THANK YOU</pattern>
        <template>You’re welcome! If you have more questions, feel free to ask!</template>
    </category>
</aiml>
